Yes, one of mine is a comparison of two stocks,
ICC Puli and ICC GI. So, first of all, the
climb in ICC Puli
is 7.37 the day before yesterday and this one of ours is of Super 45.
In its selection, like the operating
profit in it has always been in minus since March 22
and the OPM is
exactly like -4. Right now my question was
that it is still in profit, its net profit is
above 200 crores, above 200 crores. So, if
in such a company, if the climb is low and the
operating profit is in minus, then how can that net
profit be big? And
I saw the operating profit of ICC in its hands, then
only every March it goes into minus. So
I do
not have any problem with the knowledge. When I
sit for selection, I
buy it accordingly. Is this my right buy or
wrong buy? When I buy this stock,
what can happen in it?
You can see that it should be in minus, even then
we try to buy any stock
only by operating.  There is no profit, many
times there are some basics of the company which
cannot be accounted for in the sales, but the
company is getting money from steel
continuously, so other income
as it is written here, other normal
income is coming continuously, it is a
part of their business, but in some reason it cannot be categorized in above
some reason, so
because of that it is written in income,
but it is not XX,
it is written, if it is normal income, then this
normal income is consistent, it is
coming every time, we will count it,
how can you see by keeping more in it, it is not
that much Deepam, that is, it is definitely not
because other income is a
part of the business, every year, every month, that
income is coming there, like the company
invested its money in the story, some
profit was generated from there, if that profit is
dividend income, it is capital income, whatever it is,
if it is earned every year  If this is happening then the debt is D
part of D company, this business is going to come every
year basically, so there is
no need to be afraid in this, it will be less to pay
but because despite these good
profits, the
net profit of the company has decreased, which used to be 1600
crores overall, it is known that so no,
we will not buy it, it will be
better to exit from it.